/* jshint esversion: 6 */
/* jshint -W033 */

// Questions - Red
export const redQuestions = [ 
    
    {
    "question": "This is the golden age of something good and right and real",
    "answers": ["The Last Time", "State of Grace", "All Too Well", "22"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Memorizing him was as easy as knowing all the words to your old favorite song",
    "answers": ["Red", "The Lucky One", "Starlight", "Begin Again"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "I can't decide if it's a choice, getting swept away",
    "answers": ["All Too Well", "Sad Beautiful Tragic", "22", "Treacherous"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "A new notch in your belt is all I'll ever be",
    "answers": ["I Almost Do", "Stay Stay Stay", "I Knew You Were Trouble", "Holy Ground"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "But you keep my old scarf from that very first week",
    "answers": ["The Lucky One", "All Too Well", "22", "I Almost Do"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "It feels like one of those nights we won't be sleepin'",
    "answers": ["22", "The Moment I Knew", "The Last Time", "Holy Ground"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Oh, we made quite a mess, babe",
    "answers": ["Sad Beautiful Tragic", "I Almost Do", "Stay Stay Stay", "The Lucky One"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "But you carry my groceries and now I'm always laughing",
    "answers": ["Stay Stay Stay", "22", "Treacherous", "All Too Well"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Put my name at the top of your list",
    "answers": ["Everything Has Changed", "The Lucky One", "Red", "The Last Time"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Spinning like a girl in a brand new dress",
    "answers": ["Red", "Holy Ground", "The Moment I Knew", "Stay Stay Stay"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Silence, the train runs off its tracks",
    "answers": ["22", "The Last Time", "Sad Beautiful Tragic", "All Too Well"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "'Cause you don't feel pretty, you just feel used",
    "answers": ["The Lucky One", "Stay Stay Stay", "Everything has Changed", "Holy Ground"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "And all I feel in my stomach is butterflies",
    "answers": ["Treacherous", "Everything has Changed", "Red", "All Too Well"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Like, `Oh my, what a marvelous tune` it was the best night, never would forget how we moved",
    "answers": ["Red", "22", "Starlight", "Treacherous"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "I've been spending the last eight months thinking all love ever does is break and burn, and end",
    "answers": ["Everything has Changed", "Stay Stay Stay", "Holy Ground", "Begin Again"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "And there in the bathroom I try not to fall apart",
    "answers": ["The Lucky One", "The Moment I Knew", "22", "All Too Well"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "This is falling in love in the cruelest way, this is falling for you and you are worlds away",
    "answers": ["Come Back...Be Here", "The Last Time", "Red", "Treacherous"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "You understand perfectly, you're the kind of man who makes me sad",
    "answers": ["22", "Girl at Home", "Red", "All Too Well"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Love is a ruthless game unless you play it good and right ",
    "answers": ["State of Grace", "22", "Holy Ground", "Treacherous"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Now I'm lyin' on the cold hard ground",
    "answers": ["The Last Time", "The Lucky One", "Girl at Home", "I Knew You Were Trouble"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Autumn leaves falling down like pieces into place",
    "answers": ["Holy Ground", "Treacherous", "All Too Well", "Sad Beautiful Tragic"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Back to a first glance feeling on New York time",
    "answers": ["Holy Ground", "The Lucky One", "Stay Stay Stay", "Red"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "We both wake in lonely beds in different cities",
    "answers": ["The Last Time", "Sad Beautiful Tragic", "State of Grace", "Treacherous"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "The whole place was dressed to the nines",
    "answers": ["Red", "Holy Ground", "Starlight", "Girl at Home"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "And you throw your head back laughing like a little kid",
    "answers": ["The Lucky One", "Stay Stay Stay", "I Almost Do", "Begin Again"],
    "correct": 3
    },
];